lalate.com 2019-06-06

# Privacy Policy

**LALATE PRIVACY POLICY**  
**Last Updated: May 23. 2018**

lalate.com Cares About Your Privacy. Subscribers’ privacy is imperative at lalate.com. We want our subscribers fully informed about the use of their personal information prior to their choosing to subscribe to lalate.com.

**Our Policy**  
Certain sections of lalate.com engages in permission-based marketing and collects information provided by our subscribers at our, and affiliated, websites. Subscribers must provide their email address and categories of special interests. lalate.com confirms all subscriptions via email. After confirmation, at which time the subscriber has “opted-in,” lalate.com will assure the authenticity of the record by matching it against our database of consumers. lalate.com may then send you offers for goods and services relevant to your categories of interest.

Additionally, as part of our effort to bring lalate.com subscribers the best possible offers, subscribers will receive special offers that would be of value to any online consumer. lalate.com values your privacy. Our subscribers’ email addresses will only be shared with third parties where (i) third party has sufficiently demonstrated to lalate.com that their product or service is a direct match for a subscriber’s special interests (ii) if compelled to do so by proper judicial or governmental authorities. With the exception of email transmissions conducted by a third party to its customer database, all email transmissions will be conducted by lalate.com. lalate.com databases are proprietary. However, lalate.com does, provide discretionary “optional” information such as name, postal address, zip code, age, gender, etc. to third parties for non-electronic media. lalate.com always provides notice and choice to all subscribers. Once, a subscriber un-subscribes and chooses to be removed from lalate.com, the subscriber will no longer receive any offers from lalate.com unless the subscriber later opts-in. To opt-out, click [HERE.](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#!/)

**Cookies**  
Cookies are randomly generated to track unique customer conversions. No personal information is ever stored within such cookies. lalate.com tracks responses to advertising campaigns; however, lalate.com does not track subscriber web browsing activities. Please note that some of our customers’ websites may use cookies; therefore, it is recommended that our subscribers take the time to review the privacy policies, when provided, of any websites prior to entering their information.

When you visit our website, we may assign your computer one or more cookies, to facilitate access to our site and to personalize your online experience. Through the use of a cookie, we also may automatically collect information about your online activity on our site, such as the web pages you visit, the links you click, and the searches you conduct on our site. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, please note that you may not be able to sign in or use some of the interactive features offered on our website. You may also clear or delete existing cookies from standard internet browsers.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

**Use of Web Beacons**  
lalate.com does not use web beacons, Clear Gifs or Web Bugs in relation to the lalate.com website.

**Access to Account Information**  
**Consumers**  
Consumers may access their account information by contacting lalate.com via the internet at info@lalate.com.Subscribers can easily unsubscribe! Simply email us at info@lalate.com.

**Business Users**  
If you no longer wish to be contacted by lalate.com regarding our business services please contact us at info@lalate.com.

**Contests/Surveys**  
From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name, telephone number and email address). We use this information to solicit business, notify contest, winners and award prizes.

**Legal Disclaimer**  
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

**Your Information is Protected**  
All subscriber data in the lalate.com are maintained in our data center utilizing the technologies to secure, house, and serve the data. All data is housed on redundant servers and protected by a firewall and unparalleled security infrastructure. lalate.com encourages you to revisit our Privacy Statement to keep informed of any changes.

**LALATE is fully compliant with CAN-SPAM Act of 2003.**

**Third-Parties**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click [here](http://bit.ly/agb0QJ).

**Data Transfer Statement, GDPR**  
This LALATE LLC Data Transfer Statement (“Statement”) sets forth LALATE’s policies and practices concerning the transfer of personal data across borders.

**Applicability**  
This Statement applies to LALATE LLC and its U.S. operating businesses, as identified below (collectively and for this statement only, “LALATE”, “we”, or “us”). This Statement forms a part of each LALATE entity’s privacy policy:  
Operating Entity | Representative Platform | Privacy Policy  
LALATE LLC | LALATE (or LALATE.com) | https://news.lalate.com/privacy

LALATE is based in the United States. We provide services globally using computer systems, servers, and databases located in the U.S. When you use our services from outside of the U.S., your information will therefore be transferred to, stored in, and processed in the U.S. Data is collected, stored, used, and shared as set forth in our privacy policies.

**European Users**  
The European Commission has determined that the transfer of personal information of its residents outside of Europe must be subject to a legal framework that adequately protects it. We transfer personal information of European Economic Area (“EEA”) residents to the U.S. (or elsewhere) based upon the following legal frameworks:  
Legitimate business interests: We could not provide our services or comply with our obligations to you without transferring your personal information to the U.S.  
Consent: We may transfer your personal information when we receive your express, revocable consent.

**GDPR**  
We comply with the European Union’s General Data Protection Law (“GDPR”), which governs the protection of personal data of EU residents. To find out more about GDPR, please visit the European Union’s website, at https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection_en. EU users have the rights to: opt out of cookies (see our Cookie Policy); access, correct, delete, restrict or object to our use of their personal information; be forgotten; and data portability. We enable exercise of these rights through our products (which we reserve the right to modify). We also fulfil our obligations in response to direct requests. If you require assistance, please contact our Data Protection Officer. We may require additional information from you to fulfill your requests. We may charge a reasonable fee if your request imposes an unreasonable cost on us. We will afford UK-based users with all rights available to EU users, regardless of the UK’s EU member status.

**Controllers and Processors**  
Some laws, including the GDPR, differentiate between controllers and processors of data. A “controller” has a direct relationship with you and exercises control over the use of your data. The third-party vendors that help a controller provide a service are considered “processors” because they process the controller’s customer data at the controller’s request (examples are payment processors and cloud-based hosting providers).

All LALATE entities are controllers of personal information on users who set up an account on LALATE.COM. You do not need to set up an account on LALATE to read LALATE news articles.

**Dispute Resolution**  
We are committed to working with you to obtain a fair resolution of any complaint. We encourage you to begin by contacting our Data Protection Officer. We endeavor to respond to requests promptly. If you believe that we have not been able to address your complaint, you may seek redress through other means. For any questions, inquiries, or complaints, please contact us at Data Protection Officer at the physical address listed in our contact page.
